https://www.etranscriptionsolutions.org/privacy-policy

Home » Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you Upload to our website.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.etranscriptionsolutions.org
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on March 12, 2010
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
www.etranscriptionsolutions.org
493 Gateway Drive
Logan, Ohio 43138
USA
(740)385-5994
Live Chat
Follow Us!
Transcription Services
Advisory Board TranscriptionAnalyst Road Show TranscriptionBoard Meeting TranscriptionBoard of Directors TranscriptionBrainstorming Session TranscriptionBroadcast TranscriptionConvention TranscriptionDistance Learning TranscriptionDocumentary TranscriptionEthnography Research TranscriptionFinancial Presentation TranscriptionFocus Group Transcription
General TranscriptionGovernment Hearings, Briefings and Press Conference TranscriptionInsurance Statement TranscriptionInterview TranscriptionLecture TranscriptionLegal TranscriptionMedical Marketing Communication TranscriptionMilitary Exercise TranscriptionProduct Marketing Communication Transcription
Product Marketing Communication TranscriptionQuarterly and Fiscal Year-End Conference Call TranscriptionReference checks for High-End Executive TranscriptionResearch TranscriptionRound Table TranscriptionSales MeetingsSeminar TranscriptionSpeech TranscriptionSymposia TranscriptionTeleconference TranscriptionTrade Show TranscriptionWitness Statement Transcription
Sitemap | Privacy Policy
© 2020 eTranscription Solutions | Website by Bates Web Design
